[bright music]
What are you doing, bestfriend?
Are you listening to me?
I’m preparing food for work later.
Cost-cutting measures.
I'm leaving in a while.
Did you reach out to
the festival organizers?
They might know the scammer!
Yes, I sent them an e-mail.
Did they reply?
They said they’re not
related with the scammer.
They didn’t even know who he is.
They said I should file a police report.
Why don’t you post it on
social media, bestfriend?
That way the scammer will be exposed!
No!
It will spread like wildfire!
People like you love to gossip.
And I don’t want mom to worry.
I don’t want her to find
out that I threw away
all her savings for
that stupid membership.
If I were there, I would
kick him in the butt!
What now, bestfriend?
When is your flight back home?
You’re about to start another film, right?
In two days.
But I might extend my stay here.
I don’t want to go back home
without my mom’s savings.
I won’t stop until I find that swindler.
Bestfriend, if you need anything,
I’ll be glad to help.
I can send you 2,000 pesos.
I know that’s not a lot.
But at least, you’ll have
some money to buy Jollibee.
Wait, is there even a Jollibee store there?
Yeap, there is.
And thank you so much, besfriend.
But keep your money.
I’ll be fine.
Sorry, bestfriend.
My roommate’s going to use the bathroom.
I’ll talk to you later.
Bye, bestfriend.
[door opens]
You know the bathroom
has more important purposes
than making long phone calls, yeah?
Sorry.
Uh, hey, can I ask you something?
What?
Do you know where I can
find some work here in LA?
Why are you looking for work?
I thought you have a very
exclusive Hollywood project lined up?
Oh, uh, yeah.
No, of course, um...
I just got an update from
the Hollywood Executive today
and it’s going great, uh, great stuff.
Cool.
So why are you looking for work?
Oh, well, you know,
production hasn’t yet started
and I just thought I would make
myself busy in the meantime.
Uh, do you know any
other Filipinos here in LA?
No.
Okay, I don’t think I can help you.
Okay, well, um, if you think
of anyone or something…
I’m in a rush. I have to get to work.
By the way, uh, my name is Andre.
What was your name again?
Joshua.
Thanks, Joshua. I really appreciate it.
Appreciate what?
For helping me out.
[bright music]
No one’s helping you out.
You only get to stay here for one
week because you gave me $300.
If you give me another 300,
you can stay here another week.
That’s it. No more, no less.
Besides, I’m just after
your money, remember?
Can we please let that one pass?
I said I was sorry, and if I could take
my words back, I absolutely would.
Yeah, the thing about words is
there’s no way to take them
back once you’ve said them.
Uh, so unless you’ve got cash,
we have nothing to talk about.
Six days and you’re out.
[bright music]
What?
Oh, sorry. I was just wondering, um…
Oh if… if you knew where
the spare keys were.
I, um,
I might go out later.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry, Van.
I forgot.
Van?
What?
You… you just called me Van.
My name is Andre.
I know.
So, who’s Van?
No one.
I’m bad at names.
Alright.
Your keys are here.
Do you have any other questions?
No.
[bright music]
Thanks, Josh.
Excuse me. What did you just call me?
Uh, Josh?
I thought I told you my name is Joshua.
And isn’t Josh short for Joshua?
I didn't give you permission
to call me by that name.
Sorry. I didn't think I need
permission to call you Josh
since it’s pretty much the
universal short name for Joshua.
And you just called me
Van like two minutes ago.
Whatever.
Six days.
And you're out.
Whatever.
Six days. And you're out.
I didn't give you permission
to call me Joshua.
Geez!
Coming from somebody who doesn’t
want to be called selfish and greedy.
Oh, hi Josh...
...ua.
Are you talking to yourself?
No, uh, I was just practicing.
I have a rehearsal later, so...
Whatever.
Six days. And you're out.
[bright music]
Oh.
What the hell are you doing?
I was...
I was just, um, looking for my…
my underwear,
which is, um...
You're holding it.
Yeah, yeah, um…
I just... Sorry, I'm just...
Let’s take a shower.
I...
I mean I'm...
I'm going to take a shower.
Not… not you and…
I’m… I’m gonna…
Okay, I’m gonna go.
[bright music]
[piano music]
Hello, who’s this?
You didn’t save my number?
Why would I? I don't know you.
I'm the greedy, selfish guy
who's just after your money.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yes, you are.
Or not that you’re greedy and selfish,
just that you’re my kind
and caring roommate.
Anyway, sorry I didn’t save
your number. It's just that -
Yeah, I don’t care about that.
Um, I just wanted to
ask, are you free tonight?
Uh, are you asking me out on a…
What the hell are you talking about?
Easy, easy, okay?
I just thought maybe
you’re asking me out as a...
friend.
We're not friends.
And I don't need company,
especially not with you.
Okay, so why –
I got something for you.
Like a gift?
No, why would I do that?
You just said you got me something.
I got a gig.
Oh.
Really?
Yeah, um, let’s see. It’s four hours.
Uh, 50 bucks.
50 dollars? Hold on.
2,500 pesos?
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure. I’m free.
I’m definitely free.
Okay, I’ll text you the location.
Yeah, okay. I’ll be there.
And I just wanna say…
Hello?
I just wanna say thank
you for thinking about me.
[bright music]
Hi, son. How are you?
Uh...
I’m okay. How about you?
I’m not feeling well.
What?
Are you okay?
Did you go to the doctor?
No need.
I’ll take some medicines, get some rest,
then go back to work.
But you’re sick, mom.
Don’t worry about me.
I’m fine.
Let’s talk about you. How has it been?
By the way, I saw a post on Facebook.
Did you win another award?
Yes, mom. Grand Jury
Award for my short film.
Wow! Congrats, son!
Every time I hear your achievements,
all my stress and anxiety disappear.
Then, you will start another film project
when you go back to the Philippines?
Yes, mom. My script got selected.
They’ll give initial
funding for my new film.
I don’t know what to say, son.
You’re amazing!
But where are you headed now?
Why are you dressed up?
I have a gig, mom.
Look at you.
Just a few days in America
and you already got a gig?
Son, in case you need to buy anything,
just spend the money I’ve
been sending you, okay?
Don’t worry about it.
It’s just money.
I’m concerned about you.
Everything is so expensive there.
You’re spending in dollars, not pesos.
Mom, the truth is…
What is it, son?
[piano music]
I received an offer here.
From a Hollywood Executive.
Really?
That’s the best news I’ve heard!
Thank you, Lord!
Suddenly, my fever is gone.
I’m very happy for you.
You’re slowly achieving your dreams.
Okay, son.
I don’t want to keep you
from your appointment.
I’ll call you again next time.
Okay, mom.
Love you.
Okay, love you too.
Always take care, okay?
Bye.
[footsteps]
Gig in a liquor store?
Or maybe this is just a meeting place?
[street noise]
Oh.
Hi, Josh... ua.
Are you going to the Oscars or something?
No, I’m here for the gig you told me about.
Why? Am I late?
- Or is it cancelled? - No, no.
Why, why this?
Well, I assumed it has
something to do with an event.
We’re in LA, right?
Everything here is
about events and parties?
Where did you get that idea?
Here.
I need you to take these out. I’m
gonna show you how to use the register.
Oh.
So I’m going to be a…
Sorry to disappoint you.
I mean, this is not, uh,
an awards ceremony.
If you don’t want to…
No, no, I didn’t mean to say…
I just...
I just wish you had told me sooner.
But, um...
Yeah, no, it's...
What gave you the idea
that I do parties or events?
Well, you always come home late at night.
Okay.
What if I’m a caretaker for a
family and I have late night shifts?
What if I’m a waiter? Or a
movie theater employee?
I don’t know how you’re
gonna work dressed like that.
No, it’s fine. Don’t worry about it.
[bright music]
See? Problem solved.
Now, uh, where do I put these?
So look at the price tag
attached to every item
and for card transactions,
just have people insert
or swipe right here.
That’s it?
Yeah, that’s it.
I’ll be back by 10.
Where are you going?
None of your business.
- Oh, you’re going on a date.
- Just do your work
and only call me if you need something.
Got it.
Oh, by the way,
take care.
Will you stop being so…
So?
Annoying.
Me saying take care annoys you?
I say take care to all of my friends.
I’ll say this again.
We’re not friends.
We’re roommates.
Fine.
To my roommate who refuses to be my friend,
take care.
[bright music]
Hi. How can I help you?
Marlboros.
Come again?
Can I get some Marlboros? Are you deaf?
You can remove it.
Fucking Asian.
Excuse me, what did you just call me?
I said fucking Asian.
Do you have a problem with that?
Yeah.
Maybe I do.
I'm back.
Andre?
Hello?
Where are you?
What happened to your face?
Are you sure you don’t want
to report the incident, or...
Um, no, it’s fine.
I don't wanna...
I don't wanna make a scene.
Have you eaten anything yet tonight?
I'm okay.
I’ll fix you something.
- No, you really don’t have to.
- Just sit down. Wait.
- But I - - Stop.
Just stop.
You have to be extra
careful out there, okay?
It’s not safe.
[footsteps]
Kimchi.
Why? You don’t like it?
Nah, are you kidding me?
Korean food’s my favorite.
Well, after adobo and sinigang, of course.
Hmm... and rice too!
You know,
this is starting to look and
feel like a real K-drama.
Do you watch K-dramas?
They’re very popular in Asia,
especially in the Philippines.
Shut up and eat.
And they’re good too, huh.
[bright music]
Oh, you’re not gonna eat with me?
No.
Well, if this were a real K-drama,
we would definitely be eating together.
Especially after I got hurt.
This would be the part where
the two main characters -
We’re not in a Korean drama.
Stop being cheesy.
You’ll take back your words
if you actually watch K-drama.
But this looks good.
Thank you.
Oh.
50 dollars,
a nice and caring roommate,
and a delicious meal.
And you know,
if this were a K-drama,
this would be the part
where you treat my wound.
And you stare into my eyes,
then you slowly, ever so slowly realize...
Okay, well, there’s ice in the freezer,
if you wanna go grab that.
Don’t you wanna get it for me?
And just put it on my eye gently.
- Put it on my face. - What the hell? No.
But...
But it hurts so much.
It's so painful.
Oh my God.
[bright music]
Fine. Maybe I’m not a good actor.